export default Data = [
    {
        question: "1 x 1 =",
        options: ["4","2","1","5"],
        correct_option: "1"
    },
    {
        question: "1 x 2 =",
        options: ["3","2","1","5"],
        correct_option: "2"
    },
    {
        question: "1 x 3 =",
        options: ["4","2","1","3"],
        correct_option: "3"
    },
    {
        question: "1 x 4 =",
        options: ["4","8","5","2"],
        correct_option: "4"
    },
    {
        question: "1 x 5 =",
        options: ["6","2","10","5"],
        correct_option: "5"
    },
    {
        question: "1 x 6 =",
        options: ["4","7","1","6"],
        correct_option: "6"
    },
    {
        question: "1 x 7 =",
        options: ["7","21","8","5"],
        correct_option: "7"
    },
    {
        question: "1 x 8 =",
        options: ["4","8","0","1"],
        correct_option: "8"
    },
    {
        question: "1 x 9 =",
        options: ["10","8","9","1"],
        correct_option: "9"
    },
    {
        question: "1 x 10 =",
        options: ["9","1","11","10"],
        correct_option: "10"
    },
    {
        question: "2 x 1 =",
        options: ["9","2","11","10"],
        correct_option: "2"
    }
]